https://www.chainreactiondiscgolf.com/about/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Chain Reaction Disc Golf
Chain Reaction Disc Golf is based in Austin, TX and has been an online vendor since 1997. Please CONTACT-US for our email information. Our phone number is: 512-825-6054. Our website address is: https://www.chainreactiondiscgolf.com.
Your contact information
We collect information from users that register on our website and store the personal information they provide in their user profile. We also collect your transaction information when you place an order as a visitor of this website. We will collect and store your name, address, phone number, and email address in your account’s private profile. Your past orders are collected and stored for easier access —so you can review your past orders when signed into your account dashboard.
Payment information
Customers payment information is not collected and all payments are securely processed through Paypal. None of your credit card or Paypal account information is ever collected, and we never have access to your credit card or Paypal accounts or any payment information. Paypal requires your email address and shipping address for all orders.
We share data with Paypal
Chain Reaction Disc Golf is required to use your email address for payment processing through Paypal. Paypal also requires shipping address and full name for security reasons. CRDG has no access to your paypal account and does not collect or share your Paypal information.
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy
Mailing list
Please let us know if you would like to join our mailing list. Please use this MAILING LIST link for more information. You will not be entered into our mailing list unless you join through this agreement. Placing an order from Chain Reaction Disc Golf’s website will not add you to our mailing list. Our mailing list is sent out on a monthly basis and includes no more than 12 mailings in a year—from Jan. 1 to Dec. 31. We use your contact information for our monthly email and your information will not be shared with any 3rd party.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from YouTube videos behave in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Chain Reaction Disc Golf uses Google Analytics to analyze users activity, which is used to improve the functionality of our website. This insight is used for marketing purposes and to create a better experience on our website. We use cookies to gather information about the customers browser type, server, language, and relevant product search information.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website, we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). The Website administrator can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we may also send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
How we protect your data
Chain Reaction Disc Golf secures our website and customer’s information through various technical measures such as encryption and SSL data transfer protection. All information is sent through an incrypted Secure Socket Layer [SSL] with strong 2048-bit RSA keys.
We have measures in place to protect against hacking, infecting, and/or taking this site hostage. Our Wordfense Security blocks thousands of malicious attacks and all foreign IP addresses are blocked from this site. We have programs in place to immediately deal with data breaches, either potential or real.
×
INFO LINKS
About Us
How To Order
My Account
Shipping Information
Discount Code
Questions & Answers
